razorfish.com 2010-12-09

# privacy ::Razorfish

Terms of Use

ACCEPTANCE OF TERMS  
Your use of the Razorfish LLC (“Razorfish”) Web site is subject to the following Terms of Use ("TOU"). Razorfish reserves the right to update the TOU at any time without notice to you.

PRIVACY AND PROTECTION OF PERSONAL INFORMATION  
See the privacy statement for disclosures relating to the collection and use of your information.

WEB SITE CONTENT  
All content available on this web site is the copyrighted work of Razorfish and its suppliers.

Any reproduction or redistribution of this Web site, in whole or in part, without the written permission of Razorfish (or suppliers, as applicable) is expressly prohibited by law, and may result in severe civil and criminal penalties. Elements of Web sites are protected by copyright, trade dress, trademark, unfair competition, and other laws and may not be copied or imitated in whole or in part. No logo, graphic, sound or image from any Razorfish Web site may be copied or retransmitted unless expressly permitted by Razorfish. Violators will be prosecuted to the maximum extent possible.

Razorfish and/or its respective suppliers make no representations about the suitability of the information or content contained in the web site for any purpose. All such materials are provided "as is" without warranty of any kind. Razorfish and/or its respective suppliers hereby disclaim all warranties and conditions with regard to the web site, including all warranties and conditions of merchantability, whether express, implies or statutory, fitness for a particular purpose, title and non-infringement. In no event shall Razorfish and/or its respective suppliers be liable for any special, indirect or consequential damages or any damages whatsoever resulting from loss of use, data or profits, whether in an action of contract, negligence or other tortious action, arising out of or in connection with the use or performance of information available from the web site. The web site may include inaccuracies or typographical errors. Changes are periodically made to the web site, and Razorfish and/or its respective suppliers may make improvements and/or changes to the web site at any time and without any notice.

NO UNLAWFUL OR PROHIBITED USE  
As a condition of your use of the Web site, you will not use the Web site for any purpose that is unlawful or prohibited by these terms, conditions, and notices. You may not use the Web site in any manner that could damage, disable, overburden, or impair any Razorfish server, or the network(s) connected to any Razorfish server, or interfere with any other party's use and enjoyment of the Web site. You may not attempt to gain unauthorized access to the Web site, other accounts, computer systems or networks connected to any Razorfish server, through hacking, password mining or any other means. You may not obtain or attempt to obtain any materials or information through any means not intentionally made available through the Web site.

LINKS TO THIRD PARTY SITES  
The links in the web site will let you leave Razorfish's site. The linked sites are not under the control of Razorfish and Razorfish is not responsible for the contents of any linked site or any link contained in a linked site, or any changes or updates to such sites. Razorfish is not responsible for webcasting or any other form of transmission received from any linked site. Razorfish is providing these links to you only as a convenience, and the inclusion of any link does not imply endorsement by Razorfish of the linked site.

UNSOLICITED IDEA SUBMISSION POLICY  
Razorfish will not accept or consider unsolicited ideas, including ideas for new advertising, campaigns, new promotions, new products or technologies, processes, materials, marketing plans or new product names. Please do not send any original creative artwork, samples, demos or other works. The sole purpose of this policy is to avoid potential misunderstandings or disputes when Razorfish's products or marketing strategies might seem similar to ideas submitted to Razorfish. So, please do not send your unsolicited ideas to Razorfish or anyone at Razorfish. If, despite our request that you not send us your ideas and materials, you still send them, please understand that Razorfish makes no assurances that your ideas and materials will be treated as confidential or proprietary.

*****

Privacy

Last updated October 20, 2008

Razorfish and its affiliates are committed to protecting users’ privacy, and we want to keep you informed of our privacy practices through this web site. This privacy policy applies to those Razorfish and affiliate web sites that link to this notice. We encourage you to read this policy to ensure you understand our privacy practices.

Some of our clients provide Razorfish and its affiliates with personally identifiable information about their customers so we can perform various services such as online campaign analysis. In addition, as part of our services, we may collect information about user interaction with client web sites and provide that information along with our analysis to the client. All of this information belongs to the client and, as their customer, you should review the privacy policies of the sites you visit. Razorfish and its affiliates make no other use of this personally identifiable information. 

The responsible use of cookies and web beacons (aka: action tags or pixel gifs) plays an important role in the services Razorfish and its affiliates provide to clients. Our services allow our clients to better serve you, their customer. Razorfish and its affiliates may use cookie and web beacon technology for planning, serving, analyzing, and managing online campaigns on behalf of our clients. 

For more information about the use of cookies, web beacons, and how you can opt out of Atlas cookies, please review the Atlas privacy policy. In addition, depending on your web browser, you may be able to change how your computer treats cookies so that cookies are not used or saved. Please check with your browser provider for more information on managing cookies.

EMAIL SERVICE ON BEHALF OF RAZORFISH OR AFFILIATE CLIENTS  
When we conduct an e-mail campaign for our clients, we generally use e-mail service providers. Razorfish or its affiliates may use cookie and web beacon technology provided by Atlas to track the campaign's effectiveness. Generally, we do not have access to the e-mail addresses or any personally identifiable information and do not associate cookie data with any person. If we handle the e-mail addresses ourselves in conjunction with an online campaign, we do not use Atlas technology for analysis of the campaign's effectiveness, but rather rely on the e-mail service provider or the client's own cookie or web beacon technology to do so. This ensures that no personally identifiable information of our clients’ customers is associated with Atlas cookies for any purpose. 

RAZORFISH AND AFFILIATE WEB SITES   
The Razorfish and affiliate web sites provide users with information about products and services, as well as company contact information. We do not collect personal information unless you provide it to us for items such as newsletter subscriptions. We will express our need for the personal information at the point of collection and will not collect more personal information than is needed to execute your request. 

Personal information is any information that can be used to identify an individual, and may include, but is not limited to, name, email address, postal or other physical address, telephone number and other information required to provide a service, deliver a product, or carry out a transaction you have requested. 

We will only use your personal information in the way we specified when it was collected. We will not subsequently change the way your personal information is used without your consent.

We may respond to subpoenas, court orders, or legal process by disclosing your personal information and other related information, if necessary. We also may disclose your personal information to establish or exercise our legal rights or defend against legal claims.

POLICY UPDATES OR CHANGES   
Razorfish and its affiliates may update or change this privacy policy at any time and such changes will become effective 30 days after they are posted unless otherwise stated. Our web site will state the date it was last updated and we encourage you to review our privacy policy whenever you use this web site. 

We hope you find this information helpful. Our goal is to present all the information in a format that is as readable as possible. Whatever you decide to do, we want you to be completely informed about how cookies work, and how we use information on the Internet. 

Should you have any additional questions, please send an e-mail to privacyinfo@razorfish.com or write us at:

Privacy Coordinator  
Razorfish  
821 Second Ave, Suite 1800

Frequently Asked Questions:

1\. What information is collected by the Razorfish and affiliate web sites?

2\. How do Razorfish and its affiliates use personally identifying information collected on the respective Razorfish or affiliate web sites?

3\. Do Razorfish and its affiliates share my personally identifying information with third parties?

4\. How is my personally identifying information used when I apply for a position with Razorfish or an affiliate?

5\. How is my personally identifying information used when I submit it for consideration regarding partnership opportunities?

6\. How do Razorfish and its affiliates safeguard personally identifying information?

7\. What are my choices? How do I opt-out of the web site specific mailing lists and services?

8\. Can I review and delete my personally identifying information collected by the Razorfish or affiliate web sites?

9\. Do the Razorfish and affiliate web sites use cookies and web beacons?

10\. Do Razorfish or its affiliates host any blogs?

11\. Do the Razorfish and affiliate web sites link to third party web sites?

1\. What information is collected by the Razorfish and affiliate web sites?

Like most standard web site servers, we use log files. We may collect Internet protocol (IP) addresses, browser type, Internet service provider (ISP), referring/exit pages, platform type, date/time stamp, and number of clicks to analyze trends, administer the site, and track user's movement in the aggregate. The other information we collect through the Razorfish or affiliate web site is contact information you choose to provide as a consumer, client or partner, when you complete a form to request more information about our company, products or services.

back to top

2\. How do Razorfish or its affiliates use personally identifying information collected on the respective Razorfish or affiliate web site?

We use the contact information you provide to respond to your request or to provide you future updates. We may contact you through any of the means you identified on the form (e.g., phone, fax, e-mail). If you contact us as a prospective client and a business relationship is not established with Razorfish or an affiliate within a reasonable time period, we will delete your contact information.

back to top

3\. Do Razorfish and its affiliates share my personally identifying information with third parties?

We may share the contact information you provide on our web site with our contractors and vendors in order to provide a requested service or transaction (e.g., to send you an e-mail) subject to our confidentiality policies. Other than agents who act on our behalf, information you provide at this site will not be transferred or sold to unrelated third parties, unless we have your permission to do so. We may disclose your personal information to respond to subpoenas, court orders, legal process, or to protect or establish our legal rights or property. Information may be disclosed as part of any merger, acquisition, sale of company assets, as well as in the unlikely event of an insolvency, bankruptcy or receivership in which information would be transferred as one of the business assets of the company.

back to top

4\. How is my personally identifying information used when I apply for a position with Razorfish or its affiliates?

When you apply for a position with Razorfish or an affiliate, you may be linked to a third party web site. If you are linked to a third party web site, all personally identifiable information that you choose to provide, will be collected and maintained by the third party. The collection of information will be governed by the third party’s privacy policy. Razorfish or its affiliate will have access to the information that you provide to the third party. If you apply for a position with Razorfish or an affiliate directly or through a third party, and you choose to provide personally identifiable information, your personally identifiable information will be treated in accordance with this privacy policy.

back to top

5\. How is my personally identifying information used when I submit it for consideration regarding partnership opportunities?

If you are interested in partnership opportunities with Razorfish, we provide you with the opportunity to contact us through our web site. The information you can submit through our web site includes your name and contact information, information about your company, and references along with their contact information. If you choose to provide your personal information or your reference's personal information, we will use this information to assist us in determining whether to pursue a partnership opportunity with you, and will not use this information for any other purpose. We may share your personal information or your reference's personal information with our contractors and vendors to perform services for us in regard to your request (e.g., to send you an email) subject to our confidentiality policies. We will not disclose your personal information or your reference's personal information, except as otherwise described in this privacy statement. If you contact us as a prospective partner and a business relationship is not established with Razorfish or an affiliate within a reasonable time period, we will delete your contact information.

back to top

6\. How do Razorfish and its affiliates safeguard personally identifying information collected on the Razorfish and affiliate web sites?

We have security policies and procedures to protect information in our possession from loss, misuse and unauthorized access, disclosure, alteration and destruction. While no data transfer can be completely secure, we will make reasonable efforts to secure all data that is transferred, stored or processed.

back to top

7\. What are my choices? How do I opt-out of the web site-specific mailing lists and services?

After opting-in, you may choose to opt-out from any mailing lists that you have subscribed to, at any time. You may opt-out by clicking on the unsubscribe link within any of the emails that you receive. For lists and services that relate specifically to the Razorfish or affiliate web sites, you may also send your opt-out request to privacyinfo@

razorfish.com or through postal mail at:

Privacy Coordinator  
Razorfish  
821 Second Ave, Suite 1800  
Seattle, WA 98104

back to top

8\. Can I review and delete my personally identifying information collected by the Razorfish or affiliate web sites?

You can e-mail privacyinfo@

razorfish.com if you wish to access your personally identifying information. We will provide you with reasonable access to review and request the deletion of your personally identifiable information, in accordance with applicable laws and regulations.

back to top

9\. Do the Razorfish or affiliate web sites use cookies and web beacons?

The Razorfish and affiliate web sites may use persistent cookies and web beacons (aka: action tags or pixel gifs). Cookies are tiny packets of information, usually less than one kilobyte, stored in the temporary files on your hard drive, and used by web sites to recognize a computer they have encountered before. A web beacon is a clear gif not visible to the user, which collects certain anonymous information about your visit to our web sites. We use a combination of cookies and web beacons for planning, analyzing and managing our web sites. These tracking technologies collect anonymous data about users who interact with our web sites to help us provide a better user experience through the use of statistics and measurements of user satisfaction. Usage of cookies and/or web beacons is in no way linked to any personally identifiable information while on our sites.

back to top

10\. Do Razorfish or its affiliates host any blogs?

Razorfish and its affiliates may host discipline or employee blogs and may provide links to the blogs from www.razorfish.com or affiliate web sites. The postings on the blogs may include articles, press releases and research conducted by Razorfish or its affiliates. The postings on the blogs reflect the views of the authors and not necessarily those of Razorfish or its affiliates. Web site users may post comments to the blogs. In order to post a comment on a blog, you may be required to create a user name and provide your email address. Your user name and email address will be stored by Razorfish or a third party, but your name and email address will not be shared or used for any purpose beyond posting comments to the blog.  
If you use an Razorfish or affiliate blog, you should be aware that any personally identifiable information you submit there can be read, collected, or used by other users, and could be used to send you unsolicited messages. Razorfish and its affiliates are not responsible for the personally identifiable information you choose to submit in comments on our blogs.  
Some of the Razorfish or affiliate blogs may include an “email this” function. The “email this” function allows a user to send a blog posting to a friend. The “email this” function may be hosted by FeedBurner. If FeedBurner provides the “email this” function, the use of this application is governed by Feedburner’s privacy policy. Razorfish and its affiliates do not receive the email addresses that users provide to FeedBurner.

back to top

11\. Do the Razorfish and affiliate web sites link to third party web sites?

The Razorfish and affiliate web sites may provide links to third party web sites that provide valuable information. We encourage you to review the privacy policies and data collection procedures on these web sites.

back to top

Comments, Questions, or Complaints  
Please send questions, complaints, or requests for more information about the privacy policy of Razorfish and its affiliates to privacyinfo@

razorfish.com or write to us at:

Privacy Coordinator  
Razorfish  
821 Second Avenue, Suite 1800  
Seattle, WA 98104

© 2008 Razorfish LLC. All rights reserved. **  
**
